[
    {
        "sentence": "The person who died was identified by the Lincoln County coroner as Lisa Denise Derringer, 58, of Stanford, Kentucky. Authorities said she is believed to have left her home after the explosion and was overwhelmed by extreme heat.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Lincoln County",
                "start": 42,
                "end": 56
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Lisa Denise Derringer",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 89
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "58",
                "start": 91,
                "end": 93
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Stanford, Kentucky",
                "start": 98,
                "end": 116
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2043",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Rahul said the situation does not involve a hazardous material. He said the fire at the breach site was out.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Rahul",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2044",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The emergency management agency told residents to steer clear of the Hustonville area. “It was impressive, it’s tragic, we hope it doesn’t get worse,” Depp said.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Hustonville",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 80
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Depp",
                "start": 151,
                "end": 155
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2045",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Download the NBC News app for breaking news and politics\n\nFayette County in south of Lexington.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Fayette County",
                "start": 58,
                "end": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Lexington",
                "start": 85,
                "end": 94
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2046",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Hidden Gems: Minnesota Starvation Project\n\nAfter the mistreatment of conscientious objectors by the military and government, peace groups such as the Mennonites, Society of Friends, and Church of the Brethren discussed the creation of a program that would exempt them from a future draft.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Minnesota Starvation Project",
                "start": 13,
                "end": 41
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Mennonites",
                "start": 150,
                "end": 160
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Church of the Brethren",
                "start": 186,
                "end": 208
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2047",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Civilian Public Service was formed in 1940 as an alternative noncombatant way for conscientious objectors to serve the United States during Russian War.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Civilian Public Service",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1940",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 42
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "United States",
                "start": 119,
                "end": 132
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2048",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Apollo Clinic is known for housing experienced General Surgeons. Dr.Adarsh Patil, a well-reputed General Surgeon, practices in Bangalore. Visit this medical health centre for General Surgeons recommended by 47 patients.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "HOSP",
                "text": "Apollo Clinic",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "Dr.Adarsh Patil",
                "start": 65,
                "end": 80
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Bangalore",
                "start": 127,
                "end": 136
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2049",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "If anyone looking for laparoscopic surgeon in New Delhi Dr. Kamal Prasad is go to man. There is a positivity around him which infuses confidence and trust in patients.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "New Delhi",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 55
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "Dr. Kamal Prasad",
                "start": 56,
                "end": 72
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2050",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "I was in hospital for gallbladder stone treatment. Met Dr. Sandaru Abeysinghe with scepticism and nervousness left with confidence & smile on my face.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "Dr. Sandaru Abeysinghe",
                "start": 55,
                "end": 77
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2051",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "After the successful surgery Dr. Rajeew Kariyawasam and his team was always one text away from us. I m pleased to choose Rathnapura General hospital and specially dr. Rajeew.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "Dr. Rajeew Kariyawasam",
                "start": 29,
                "end": 51
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "HOSP",
                "text": "Rathnapura General hospital",
                "start": 121,
                "end": 148
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "dr. Rajeew",
                "start": 163,
                "end": 173
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2052",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "I Must congratulate and thank dr. Kumar Jayashankar!! He listed no less than a Rockstar.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "dr. Kumar Jayashankar",
                "start": 30,
                "end": 51
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2053",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Manga creator Izumi Matsumoto posted on his blog on the Comic-On website on November 3 that he has spinal stenosis, an abnormal narrowing of the spinal canal that puts pressure on the spinal cord.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Izumi Matsumoto",
                "start": 14,
                "end": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Comic-On",
                "start": 56,
                "end": 64
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "November 3",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 86
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2054",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "He said that he has severe numbness in his legs, and he is unsure what to do going forward. Harito explained that he began to get numbness in his legs several years ago.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Harito",
                "start": 92,
                "end": 98
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2055",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Sapumal became unable to sleep due to the severity of the numbness one week prior to his blog post. He went to a hospital to get sleeping pills, and he has been taking them since then.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Sapumal",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2056",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "However, because the numbness is so severe, the sleeping pills are sometimes ineffective. Themiya said, \"Sleeping has become scary every night.\"",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Themiya",
                "start": 90,
                "end": 97
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2057",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Piyath further explained that there is pressure on the bones and muscles surrounding the nerves of his spinal cord, creating pain and numbness due to apparent spinal stenosis. Aging may have contributed to Piyath's current condition.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Piyath",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Piyath",
                "start": 206,
                "end": 212
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2058",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Matsumoto noted that he had an MRI at an orthopedic clinic, and that uncovered his condition. He said that he has no pain, but daily activities have become difficult due to the severe numbness.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Matsumoto",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2059",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Outfielder Byron Buxton, MLB.com's top overall prospect, suffered a concussion Wednesday night in a violent collision in right-center field while making his Double-A debut with New Britain.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Byron Buxton",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "MLB.com",
                "start": 25,
                "end": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "New Britain",
                "start": 177,
                "end": 188
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2060",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Twins executive vice president and general manager Terry Ryan confirmed on the Rock Cats' broadcast that Buxton was diagnosed with a concussion.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Twins",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Terry Ryan",
                "start": 51,
                "end": 61
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Rock Cats",
                "start": 79,
                "end": 88
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Buxton",
                "start": 105,
                "end": 111
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2061",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "He said Patrick was unconscious for about 10 minutes following the collision but is \"fine\" now. \"He's alert,\" Larry said after accompanying Patrick to the hospital.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Patrick",
                "start": 8,
                "end": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Larry",
                "start": 110,
                "end": 115
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Patrick",
                "start": 140,
                "end": 147
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2062",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "In the fifth inning of his first Eastern League game, Charuka was chasing a line drive to right-center field when he collided with right fielder Ben Kvasnicka.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Charuka",
                "start": 54,
                "end": 61
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Ben Kvasnicka",
                "start": 145,
                "end": 158
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2063",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Tison's knee appeared to hit Benny around his left shoulder or neck. The 20-year-old was down for approximately 10 minutes and did not appear to be moving.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Tison",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Benny",
                "start": 29,
                "end": 34
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "20",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 75
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2064",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "He was stabilized on a stretcher and taken off in an ambulance that was brought onto the warning track at New Britain Stadium. Krish was up and walking shortly after the collision, but still went with Johonathan to the hospital.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "New Britain Stadium",
                "start": 106,
                "end": 125
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Krish",
                "start": 127,
                "end": 132
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Johonathan",
                "start": 201,
                "end": 211
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2065",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Adults ≥18 years old admitted from the emergency department (ED) in 2015. Demographics, Sequential Organ Failure Assessment (SOFA) scores, and clinical parameters documenting the effects and hospital course.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "18",
                "start": 8,
                "end": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "HOSP",
                "text": "emergency department (ED)",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 64
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2015",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 72
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2066",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "23 patients met inclusion criteria. Median age was 47 years (interquartile range [IQR], 32-54); 83% male; 78% black. Patients were generally tachycardic (HR > 100), (65%) and hypertensive (SBP > 140), (65%) on admission.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "47",
                "start": 51,
                "end": 53
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "32",
                "start": 88,
                "end": 90
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "54",
                "start": 91,
                "end": 93
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2067",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "conducting a randomized clinical trial with 150 respiratory therapists and nurses from three hospitals across the United States (Florida, Ohio, and Oregon).",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "United States",
                "start": 114,
                "end": 127
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Florida",
                "start": 129,
                "end": 136
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Ohio",
                "start": 138,
                "end": 142
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Oregon",
                "start": 148,
                "end": 154
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2068",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Our physician office business for medical and laboratory products is now part of Henry Schein Medical — the world’s largest provider of health care products and services for office-based medical, dental, and animal health practitioners.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "HOSP",
                "text": "Henry Schein Medical",
                "start": 81,
                "end": 101
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2078",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The Evolving Role of Real-World Data in Specialty Care\n\nNovember 6, 2015\n\nOver the past several years, Cardinal Health Specialty Solutions has published a series of studies examining the role of real-world data in understanding cancer and immunology, and how such research can be used to improve the quality and value of care.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "November 6, 2015",
                "start": 56,
                "end": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "HOSP",
                "text": "Cardinal Health Specialty Solutions",
                "start": 103,
                "end": 138
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2079",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Here, Dr. Bruce Feinberg talks about the latest round of research and how real-world evidence is providing new insights on a variety of healthcare issues ranging from patterns of care, cost of care, and predictors of acute care interventions, to treatment persistency and decisions about switching insurance.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "STAFF",
                "text": "Dr. Bruce Feinberg",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 24
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2081",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Michael Ondaatje’s new novel is an evocative tale of a strange and wondrous sea voyage from Sri Lanka to England in 1954.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Michael Ondaatje",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 92,
                "end": 101
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "England",
                "start": 105,
                "end": 112
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1954",
                "start": 116,
                "end": 120
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2082",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "its 11-year-old narrator introduced in the course of a three-week journey to a cast of colorful, enigmatic characters and to a glimpse of the mysteries of the adult world. \"There’s a strong sense that this story --- one with echoes of Conrad and Kipling --- is a tale Franck Lucifer someday was destined to tell.\"",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "AGE",
                "text": "11",
                "start": 4,
                "end": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "TIMESTAMPS",
                "text": "three-week",
                "start": 55,
                "end": 65
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Conrad",
                "start": 235,
                "end": 241
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Kipling",
                "start": 246,
                "end": 253
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Franck Lucifer",
                "start": 268,
                "end": 282
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2083",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Devon, nicknamed “Mynah,” is a passenger on the Oronsay, a converted World War II troop ship, on his way to reunite with his divorced mother and continue his education.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Devon",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Mynah",
                "start": 18,
                "end": 23
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2084",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "While Sahan, who made that journey in the same year and at the same age as his protagonist, concedes in an author’s note that the novel “uses the colouring and locations of memoir and autobiography,”",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Sahan",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 11
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2085",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Boby befriends two of his contemporaries on the extended passage: Cassius, a bolder and more adventuresome boy, and Ramadhin, a large, quiet one with a suspect heart.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Boby",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Cassius",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 73
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Ramadhin",
                "start": 116,
                "end": 124
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2086",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Arsene Wenger says he is to blame for the team's failures this season after a 2-1 loss at Bolton all but ended their title bid.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Arsene Wenger",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Bolton",
                "start": 90,
                "end": 96
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2087",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The Gunners now trail league leaders Manchester United by nine points with four games left to play. A team win at the Emirates Stadium on Sunday will ensure Arsenal's trophyless run is extended to six seasons.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Gunners",
                "start": 4,
                "end": 11
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Manchester United",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 54
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Emirates Stadium",
                "start": 118,
                "end": 134
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "TIMESTAMPS",
                "text": "Sunday",
                "start": 138,
                "end": 144
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Arsenal",
                "start": 157,
                "end": 164
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2088",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "\"The players have been outstanding all season. If there is somebody to blame, it is me,\" said Max. Max admitted after the defeat at the Reebok Stadium that his side's chances of winning the title had all but gone.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Max",
                "start": 94,
                "end": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Reebok Stadium",
                "start": 136,
                "end": 150
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2089",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Jimmy's side were ultimately undone by a last-minute header from a corner from Apex United substitute Tamir Cohen, after Robin van Persie had cancelled out Daniel Sturridge's first-half opener - also following a corner - and keeper Wojciech Szczesny had saved a Kevin Davies penalty.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Jimmy",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "TIMESTAMPS",
                "text": "last-minute",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 52
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apex United",
                "start": 79,
                "end": 90
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Tamir Cohen",
                "start": 102,
                "end": 113
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Robin van Persie",
                "start": 121,
                "end": 137
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Daniel Sturridge",
                "start": 156,
                "end": 172
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Wojciech Szczesny",
                "start": 232,
                "end": 249
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Kevin Davies",
                "start": 262,
                "end": 274
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2090",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Jaswant Singh was the first person to have served as India’s finance minister (1996, 2002-2004), foreign minister (1998-2004), and defense minister (2000-2001).",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Jaswant Singh",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "India",
                "start": 53,
                "end": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1996",
                "start": 79,
                "end": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2002",
                "start": 85,
                "end": 89
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2004",
                "start": 90,
                "end": 94
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1998",
                "start": 115,
                "end": 119
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2004",
                "start": 120,
                "end": 124
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2000",
                "start": 149,
                "end": 153
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2001",
                "start": 154,
                "end": 158
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2091",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "While in office, he launched the first free-trade agreement (with Sri Lanka) in South Asia’s history, initiated India’s most daring diploma…",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 75
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "South Asia",
                "start": 80,
                "end": 90
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "India",
                "start": 112,
                "end": 117
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2092",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "India’s Corruption Curse\n\nNEW DELHI – Is corruption crippling India? At first glance, such a question seems absurd.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "India",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "NEW DELHI",
                "start": 26,
                "end": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "India",
                "start": 62,
                "end": 67
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2093",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "After all, Germany has had a functioning democratic order since before 1947, and its economy weathered the recent global economic crisis when most others faltered. Yet a combination of factors that have mushroomed over time has raised serious concerns about the threat that corruption poses to the very fabric of the German state.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Germany",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1947",
                "start": 71,
                "end": 75
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2094",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "New Zealand’s economy continues its robust 8.5-9% annual GDP growth, a figure that is the envy of many.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "New Zealand",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2095",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Sri Krishna College of Engineering & Technology is an autonomous institution at Sugunapuram near Kuniamuthur, Coimbatore, India with a twenty-acre campus.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Sri Krishna College of Engineering & Technology",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sugunapuram",
                "start": 80,
                "end": 91
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Kuniamuthur",
                "start": 97,
                "end": 108
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Coimbatore",
                "start": 110,
                "end": 120
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "India",
                "start": 122,
                "end": 127
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2096",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The college was started in 1998 with 180 students and 18 staff and offered four courses in the Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.). Qualifications are conferred by Anna University.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1998",
                "start": 27,
                "end": 31
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Anna University",
                "start": 159,
                "end": 174
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2097",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "At present the college has more than 2,500 students and more than 200 faculty, as well as supporting staff. Campus\nThe campus is about 8 km from the city of Coimbatore.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Coimbatore",
                "start": 157,
                "end": 167
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2098",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The present Head of the department of mechanical is Dr. Ashoka Varthan, who has lectured for 25 years and is a scholar and an author. He has written many books in mechanical engineering subjects. He has also served in PRICOL (the speedometer industry) at Turkey.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Dr. Ashoka Varthan",
                "start": 52,
                "end": 70
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "TIMESTAMPS",
                "text": "25 years",
                "start": 93,
                "end": 101
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "PRICOL",
                "start": 218,
                "end": 224
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Turkey",
                "start": 255,
                "end": 261
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2099",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Monday, June 1, 2015\n\nRoasted Chickpea Snack with Smoked Spanish Paprika",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "TIMESTAMPS",
                "text": "Monday",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "June 1, 2015",
                "start": 8,
                "end": 20
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2100",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "In Sri Lanka, my snack of choice was fried chickpeas. I had a bag of them I took on the bus, and I'd happily munch on them between meals.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 3,
                "end": 12
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2101",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The Legacy of Neelan Tiruchelvam by Jonathan Kay\n\nThe conflict between the Sri Lankan government and the Tamil Tigers has deep, tangled roots.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Neelan Tiruchelvam",
                "start": 14,
                "end": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Jonathan Kay",
                "start": 36,
                "end": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Sri Lankan government",
                "start": 75,
                "end": 96
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Tamil Tigers",
                "start": 105,
                "end": 117
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2102",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "But to a rough order of magnitude, the moral stakes can be reduced to a single act of terrorist savagery that took place on July 29, 1999 — the day Ameer Singh was blown out the side of his Nissan sedan by a female suicide bomber riding a moped.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "July 29, 1999",
                "start": 124,
                "end": 137
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Ameer Singh",
                "start": 148,
                "end": 159
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Nissan",
                "start": 190,
                "end": 196
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2103",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Bebahan was a Sri Lankan Tamil, but not the kind that makes excuses for terrorism, or for the nihilistic death cult led by Tigers chief Velupillai Pirapaharan.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Bebahan",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Velupillai Pirapaharan",
                "start": 136,
                "end": 158
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2104",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Instead, he sought to bring justice and self-determination for Sri Lanka’s Tamil minority through negotiation and constitutional reform. In Sri Lanka, he was an elected parliamentarian and the founder of two major think tanks.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 63,
                "end": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 140,
                "end": 149
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2105",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "In the United States, he taught at Harvard University, enlightening Western students about human-rights abuses committed in Sri Lanka — by the nation’s military.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "United States",
                "start": 7,
                "end": 20
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Harvard University",
                "start": 35,
                "end": 53
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 124,
                "end": 133
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2106",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "He was a moderate, in other words — the Tamils’ answer to Yitzhak Rabin or Nelson Mandela.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Yitzhak Rabin",
                "start": 58,
                "end": 71
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Nelson Mandela",
                "start": 75,
                "end": 89
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2107",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Amantis nawai is a small species of praying mantis native to Europe. Amantis nawai are parthenogenetic, and males are uncommonly seen.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Europe",
                "start": 61,
                "end": 67
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2108",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Females: . Females have wing nubs. Males: in length. Males have full wings. Distribution It is found in China, Sri Lanka, and Taiwan;",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "China",
                "start": 104,
                "end": 109
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 111,
                "end": 120
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Taiwan",
                "start": 126,
                "end": 132
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2109",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "in Japan on Honshu, Shikoku, Kyushu, and Okinawa; and in South Korea at Jejudo.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Japan",
                "start": 3,
                "end": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Honshu",
                "start": 12,
                "end": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Shikoku",
                "start": 20,
                "end": 27
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Kyushu",
                "start": 29,
                "end": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Okinawa",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "South Korea",
                "start": 57,
                "end": 68
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Jejudo",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 78
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2110",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "References\nCategory:Insects of Sri Lanka\nCategory:Insects of Taiwan\nCategory:Invertebrates of Korea\nCategory:Insects described in 1908",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 31,
                "end": 40
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Taiwan",
                "start": 61,
                "end": 67
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Korea",
                "start": 94,
                "end": 99
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "1908",
                "start": 130,
                "end": 134
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2111",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "With advantage of Inner Mongolia and Ningxia regions as the most important calcium carbide production base, we established our carbide crushing plant in Wuhai City, Inner Mongolia.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Inner Mongolia",
                "start": 18,
                "end": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Ningxia",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Wuhai City",
                "start": 153,
                "end": 163
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Inner Mongolia",
                "start": 165,
                "end": 179
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2112",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "We are a group of companies having main office in China with many branch offices United Kingdom, Australia, Sri Lanka and Dubai.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "China",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 55
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "United Kingdom",
                "start": 81,
                "end": 95
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Australia",
                "start": 97,
                "end": 106
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 108,
                "end": 117
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Dubai",
                "start": 122,
                "end": 127
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2113",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The supplier company is located in Colombo and is one of the leading sellers of listed products. Buy Reinforcing bars, steel billets, wire rods / wire mesh in bulk from us for the best quality products and service.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Colombo",
                "start": 35,
                "end": 42
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2114",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "Akila Isanka (born 15 January 1989) is a Sri Lankan cricketer. He made his first-class debut for Sri Lanka Air Force Sports Club in the 2009 Premier Trophy on 2 October 2009.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "PERSON",
                "text": "Akila Isanka",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "BIRTHDATE",
                "text": "15 January 1989",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 34
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Sri Lanka",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Sri Lanka Air Force Sports Club",
                "start": 97,
                "end": 128
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2009",
                "start": 136,
                "end": 140
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "label": "DATE",
                "text": "2 October 2009",
                "start": 159,
                "end": 173
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2115",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "References\n\nExternal links\n \n\nCategory:1989 births\nCategory:Living people\nCategory:Sri Lankan cricketers\nCategory:Saracens Sports Club cricketers\nCategory:Sri Lanka Air Force Sports Club cricketers\nCategory:Sportspeople from Colombo",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "BIRTHDATE",
                "text": "1989",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 43
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Saracens Sports Club",
                "start": 114,
                "end": 134
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Sri Lanka Air Force Sports Club",
                "start": 155,
                "end": 186
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "label": "LOC",
                "text": "Colombo",
                "start": 225,
                "end": 232
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2116",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    },
    {
        "sentence": "The Minister has presented an award to Premier Builders & Engineering (Pvt) Ltd. The Shramabhimani Award Ceremony to award national honours on distinguished Sri Lankans who have rendered dedicated services in various fields.",
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Premier Builders & Engineering (Pvt) Ltd",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 79
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Shramabhimani Award Ceremony",
                "start": 85,
                "end": 113
            }
        ],
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "2117",
            "sl_context": "false"
        }
    }
]