[
    {
        "text": "Doctor: Is your work address still 23 Corporate Blvd, Chicago?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "201",
            "patient_id": "13223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 35,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patient: Dr. Susan Ray from Pine Hill Clinic diagnosed my condition.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "202",
            "patient_id": "13334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patient: My name is Nathaniel Carter. I was referred to Dr. Michelle Huang at Riverbend Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "203",
            "patient_id": "13445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 20,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 56,
                "end": 74,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 78,
                "end": 96,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Doctor: Your test results are with Dr. Kevin Morgan at Woodland Labs.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "204",
            "patient_id": "13556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 35,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 55,
                "end": 68,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patient: My child, Amelia Brown, is 5 years old.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "205",
            "patient_id": "13667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 19,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "AGE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Doctor: Please confirm if your contact number is 212-555-7890.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "206",
            "patient_id": "13778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patient: My ID number is NC901234, and I reside in Boston, MA.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "207",
            "patient_id": "13889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 25,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "ID"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Doctor: You last visited on March 12th at Northside Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "208",
            "patient_id": "13990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patient: Dr. Rachel Green prescribed my medication last month.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "209",
            "patient_id": "14001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Doctor: The billing address is 123 Maple Avenue, Los Angeles, CA.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "210",
            "patient_id": "14112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 31,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My email is emily.clark@example.com, and I work at OpenAI.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "211",
            "patient_id": "14223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Can you recall the exact date, like July 7th, of your surgery?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "212",
            "patient_id": "14334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My husband, James Parker, visited Dr. Lee Thompson at Westwood Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "213",
            "patient_id": "14445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 54,
                "end": 71,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Are you still living at 678 Elm Street, Austin, TX?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "214",
            "patient_id": "14556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 24,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My cousin, Olivia Lewis, is a pharmacist at Downtown Pharmacy.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "215",
            "patient_id": "14667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My contact number is 789-456-1230, and I work at Apple Inc.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "267",
            "patient_id": "19889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 21,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "PHONE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 49,
                "end": 58,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's confirm your ID as JL987654 for the health records.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "268",
            "patient_id": "19990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 25,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I recently moved from Austin, TX, to Boston for a new job.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "269",
            "patient_id": "20001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your last check-up was on December 10th at Green Hills Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "270",
            "patient_id": "20112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 26,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 43,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My nephew, Adam Carter, is being treated for asthma at City Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "271",
            "patient_id": "20223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 55,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dr. Susan Green at Sunshine Hospital has referred you here.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "272",
            "patient_id": "20334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 19,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I am Sophia Evans. My work number is 888-555-4321.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "273",
            "patient_id": "20445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 5,
                "end": 17,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You were seen by Dr. Daniel Brown on November 15th last year.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "274",
            "patient_id": "20556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 17,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id":2,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"

            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My dad, Michael Harris, was hospitalized at Maple Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "275",
            "patient_id": "20667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The test results from December 7th indicate a follow-up at Mercy Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "276",
            "patient_id": "20778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 59,
                "end": 73,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm Emma Thomas. My email is emma.thomas@example.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "277",
            "patient_id": "20889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 29,
                "end": 52,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "When did Dr. Richard Black at Summit Health check on you?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "278",
            "patient_id": "20990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My previous address was 456 Elm Street, San Diego, CA.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "279",
            "patient_id": "21001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 24,
                "end": 53,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I noticed your ID is ET765432. Is this correct?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "280",
            "patient_id": "21112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 21,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My uncle, Robert Brown, needs to contact Dr. Linda King at Hope Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "281",
            "patient_id": "21223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 10,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 41,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 59,
                "end": 70,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Can you confirm your last visit to Phoenix Hospital was on May 5th?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "282",
            "patient_id": "21334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 35,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 59,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm Carlos Gomez. I was born on April 3rd, 1985, in San Juan, Puerto Rico.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "283",
            "patient_id": "21445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 32,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "BIRTHDATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 52,
                "end": 73,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I see Dr. Angela Ray referred you from Pacific Health Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "284",
            "patient_id": "21556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 6,
                "end": 20,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My father's name is James Carter, and his ID is JC112233.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "285",
            "patient_id": "21667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 20,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 56,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's review the lab results from January 25th at Mercy Labs.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "286",
            "patient_id": "21778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 34,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My email is carlos.gomez@example.com, and I reside in Miami, FL.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "287",
            "patient_id": "21889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 54,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "When was your last visit to St. Vincent Hospital?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "288",
            "patient_id": "21990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My nephew, William Adams, recently went to Cedar Sinai Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "289",
            "patient_id": "22001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 43,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Did Dr. Maria Lopez recommend the check-up at Unity Medical?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "290",
            "patient_id": "22112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 46,
                "end": 59,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My workplace is TechCorp, and I was there until December 2023.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "291",
            "patient_id": "22223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 16,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your ID appears to be CG776655. Please verify this.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "292",
            "patient_id": "22334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I live on 1234 Pine Street, Los Angeles, California.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "293",
            "patient_id": "22445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 10,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Please provide the email associated with your profile, such as john.doe@example.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "294",
            "patient_id": "22556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 63,
                "end": 83,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My aunt, Sarah Johnson, went to General Health Center for treatment.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "295",
            "patient_id": "22667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 32,
                "end": 53,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You were seen on October 10th by Dr. Laura White at City Medical.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "296",
            "patient_id": "22778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 17,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 52,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My colleague, David Warner, can confirm my trip to Amazon HQ.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "297",
            "patient_id": "22889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 14,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Based on records, you last visited Mount Sinai on April 14th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "298",
            "patient_id": "22990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 35,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My child's doctor is Dr. Kevin Hart at Children's Care Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "299",
            "patient_id": "23001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 21,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Did you notice any symptoms during your trip to Seattle last month?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "300",
            "patient_id": "23112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 56,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I work at Bloomberg, and my phone number is 212-555-6789.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "301",
            "patient_id": "23223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 10,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 56,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your previous records indicate a follow-up with Dr. Emily Rose at Health Plus.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "302",
            "patient_id": "23334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 62,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 66,
                "end": 77,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I've been consulting Dr. Nathan Green at Redwood Medical Center for two months.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "303",
            "patient_id": "23445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 21,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 41,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 68,
                "end": 78,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your last blood test was on November 18th, conducted by LabCorp.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "304",
            "patient_id": "23556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 56,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My father works at Tesla, and his phone number is 987-654-3210.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "305",
            "patient_id": "23667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 19,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 62,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'll refer you to Dr. Samantha Brown at St. Luke's Hospital for further evaluation.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "306",
            "patient_id": "23778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 18,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 40,
                "end": 59,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My brother, Adam Turner, recently traveled to Paris for a conference.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "307",
            "patient_id": "23889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 46,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I have noted your ID as AT990011. Please confirm.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "308",
            "patient_id": "23990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 24,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My insurance provider is BlueShield, and I live in Austin, Texas.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "309",
            "patient_id": "24001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 25,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "When did you last speak with Dr. William Cooper at Regional Health?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "310",
            "patient_id": "24112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 29,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My daughter, Chloe Reed, studies at Stanford University.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "311",
            "patient_id": "24223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 13,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your last visit to the clinic was on August 10th this year.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "312",
            "patient_id": "24334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 49,
                "end": 58,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I can be reached at jason.bourne@example.com or 555-432-1234.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "313",
            "patient_id": "24445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 20,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's schedule your surgery at Apollo Hospital for November 20th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "314",
            "patient_id": "24556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 31,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My cousin, Olivia Blake, lives in Toronto, Canada.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "315",
            "patient_id": "24667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 34,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I will connect you to Dr. Peter Smith at General Health Services.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "316",
            "patient_id": "24778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 41,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My zip code is 94016, and I work at Meta in California.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "317",
            "patient_id": "24889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 15,
                "end": 20,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your brother's records indicate a consultation with Dr. Emily Rose at Unity Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "318",
            "patient_id": "24990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 52,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 70,
                "end": 84,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm due for a follow-up appointment at Cleveland Clinic next week.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "319",
            "patient_id": "25001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 56,
                "end": 65,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The MRI results will be available by October 15th from Mercy Labs.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "320",
            "patient_id": "25112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 55,
                "end": 65,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My boss, Samuel Lee, suggests I visit Pacific Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "321",
            "patient_id": "25223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 38,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Do you have any previous prescriptions from Dr. Nathan Young at Healthway Hospital?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "322",
            "patient_id": "25334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 64,
                "end": 82,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My full name is Sophia Green, and I recently moved to Miami, Florida.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "323",
            "patient_id": "25445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 16,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 54,
                "end": 68,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "We have your file under ID SG990088. Is that correct?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "324",
            "patient_id": "25556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 27,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My brother, Michael Foster, works for Amazon in Seattle.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "325",
            "patient_id": "25667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 38,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Please update your contact as jane.doe@example.com and 789-456-1230.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "326",
            "patient_id": "25778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 55,
                "end": 67,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I was advised by Dr. Amanda Clark to visit New Hope Hospital for tests.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "327",
            "patient_id": "25889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 17,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 43,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your last check-up was on July 20th, at Valley Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "328",
            "patient_id": "25990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 26,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 40,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My son, Liam Brown, just returned from a conference in Dubai.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "329",
            "patient_id": "26001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 18,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 55,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's review your prescription records at Central Pharmacy.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "330",
            "patient_id": "26112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 58,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My uncle, Robert Gray, lives in San Francisco, California.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "331",
            "patient_id": "26223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 10,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 32,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I see that you visited Dr. George White at Green Valley Hospital recently.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "332",
            "patient_id": "26334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 23,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 43,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My current address is 1234 Elm Street, Boston, MA 02115.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "333",
            "patient_id": "26445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your blood work from May 15th shows significant improvement.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "334",
            "patient_id": "26556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 21,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I've been consulting with Dr. Jennifer Adams at City Health Services.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "335",
            "patient_id": "26667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 26,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 68,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The results were uploaded to your account ID JS123456.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "336",
            "patient_id": "26778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 45,
                "end": 53,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I recently returned from Tokyo, Japan, and feel exhausted.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "337",
            "patient_id": "26889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 25,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "We recommend visiting Dr. Emily Brown at Hilltop Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "338",
            "patient_id": "26990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 41,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My nephew, Ethan Smith, studies computer science at MIT.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "339",
            "patient_id": "27001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 52,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your surgery is scheduled for March 8th at Springfield General Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "340",
            "patient_id": "27112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 43,
                "end": 71,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I have a question regarding Dr. Nathaniel Clarke's diagnosis.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "341",
            "patient_id": "27223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "STAFF"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Please confirm your current email, alex.jones@example.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "342",
            "patient_id": "27334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 35,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Good morning, Dr. Smith. My name is Linda Davis, and I'm here about my blood pressure.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "343",
            "patient_id": "27445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 14,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Good morning, Linda. Let me pull up your email: linda.davis@gmail.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "344",
            "patient_id": "27445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 14,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hello, Dr. Brown. I'm Martin Clark, and I'm having chest pains since last week.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "345",
            "patient_id": "27556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 7,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 69,
                "end": 78,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Martin, let's review the report from City Hospital and analyze your symptoms.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "346",
            "patient_id": "27556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My name is Sarah Green, and I recently visited Dr. Taylor at Mercy Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "347",
            "patient_id": "27667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 46,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 61,
                "end": 75,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sarah, we need to schedule a follow-up on March 10th for further evaluation.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "348",
            "patient_id": "27667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 52,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hi, Dr. Adams. I'm John White. Can you review my last test at Central Lab?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "349",
            "patient_id": "27778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 19,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 62,
                "end": 73,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "John, your last visit was on February 18th, as recorded in your file.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "350",
            "patient_id": "27778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 29,
                "end": 42,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "This is Mike Brown, and I work at Microsoft. I've had migraines since December.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "351",
            "patient_id": "27889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 18,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 34,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 70,
                "end": 78,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mike, your appointment on December 20th confirmed signs of chronic migraines.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "352",
            "patient_id": "27889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 26,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hello, I'm Natalie King, and my phone number is 987-654-3210.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "353",
            "patient_id": "27990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Natalie, I'll send a confirmation email to natalie.king@mail.com shortly.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "354",
            "patient_id": "27990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 43,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My child, Ethan Brown, had a vaccination at Sunrise Health Center last year.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "355",
            "patient_id": "28001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 10,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 65,
                "label": "HOSP",
                "text": "Sunrise Health Center"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 66,
                "end": 75,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ethan, I'll verify his vaccine record with the Health Department.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "356",
            "patient_id": "28001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm Olivia Roberts, and I just moved to San Diego, California.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "357",
            "patient_id": "28112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 18,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 40,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia, your file shows your last check-up at Bayview Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "358",
            "patient_id": "28112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 46,
                "end": 68,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My husband, Robert Lee, is being treated by Dr. Steven at Green Valley Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "359",
            "patient_id": "28223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 58,
                "end": 79,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robert's file shows significant recovery. Let's schedule a follow-up on April 5th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "360",
            "patient_id": "28223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 72,
                "end": 81,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My niece, Chloe Adams, attends a program at Stanford University.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "361",
            "patient_id": "28334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 10,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hi, my name is Emma Wilson. I need to book an appointment with Dr. Lucas at Redwood Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "362",
            "patient_id": "28445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 15,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 63,
                "end": 72,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 76,
                "end": 92,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Emma, we can schedule an appointment for you on May 15th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "363",
            "patient_id": "28445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 56,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My father, Michael Brown, recently underwent surgery at Mercy General.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "364",
            "patient_id": "28556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 56,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Michael's condition is stable. He should rest for the next two weeks.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "365",
            "patient_id": "28556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 59,
                "end": 68,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hello, I'm Ryan Carter. I work as an engineer at Tesla.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "366",
            "patient_id": "28667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 49,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ryan, we need to monitor your blood pressure and schedule follow-ups monthly.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "367",
            "patient_id": "28667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "This is Amanda Lopez. I have been experiencing severe migraines for 10 days.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "368",
            "patient_id": "28778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 20,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Amanda, we can prescribe medication. Let's also perform a neurological exam.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "369",
            "patient_id": "28778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My name is Jason Miller, and my contact number is 123-456-7890.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "370",
            "patient_id": "28889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 62,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your prescription history shows an appointment on February 14th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "216",
            "patient_id": "14778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My daughter, Sophia Martinez, is 2 years old.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "217",
            "patient_id": "14889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 13,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "AGE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Is Dr. Hannah Bell at Midtown Clinic your primary physician?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "218",
            "patient_id": "14990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 3,
                "end": 18,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My ID is KB567890, and I moved to Seattle last week.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "219",
            "patient_id": "15001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 17,
                "label": "ID"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 34,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "We reviewed your results from Ridgeview Diagnostics dated May 10th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "220",
            "patient_id": "15112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 58,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Please call me at 987-654-3210 to discuss further details.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "221",
            "patient_id": "15223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 18,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Did Dr. William Carter confirm the diagnosis last December?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "222",
            "patient_id": "15334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 45,
                "end": 58,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My name is Abigail Johnson, and my ID is AJ12345.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "223",
            "patient_id": "15445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 41,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Thank you, Abigail. Let's verify your address at 456 Pine Street, Denver, CO.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "224",
            "patient_id": "15556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 18,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 49,
                "end": 76,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My brother, Ethan White, was treated by Dr. Sarah King at Sunshine Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "225",
            "patient_id": "15667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 40,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 58,
                "end": 73,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your last appointment was on April 3rd at Green Valley Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "226",
            "patient_id": "15778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 29,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My email is ethan.white@samplemail.com, and I live in San Francisco.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "227",
            "patient_id": "15889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 54,
                "end": 67,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Please contact our office at 310-555-9876 for further discussion.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "228",
            "patient_id": "15990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 29,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My son, Benjamin Cooper, is 8 years old and under observation.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "229",
            "patient_id": "16001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "AGE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Did Dr. Michael Brown review your report on March 15th?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "230",
            "patient_id": "16112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I was prescribed medication by Dr. Jane Doe at Harborview Medical Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "231",
            "patient_id": "16223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 31,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 47,
                "end": 72,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Can you provide your address as 89 Elm Avenue, Seattle, WA?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "232",
            "patient_id": "16334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 32,
                "end": 58,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My husband, Kevin Adams, visited Dr. Robert Hill at Memorial Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "233",
            "patient_id": "16445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 52,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your next appointment is scheduled for May 10th at Clearview Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "234",
            "patient_id": "16556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 67,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I have an email registered under abigail.johnson@mail.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "235",
            "patient_id": "16667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's review your test results from Lakeside Diagnostic Center dated April 2nd.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "236",
            "patient_id": "16778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 62,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 69,
                "end": 78,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My ID number is BC67890, and I am moving to Chicago.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "237",
            "patient_id": "16889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 16,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "ID"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The contact number for the pharmacy is 555-987-6543.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "238",
            "patient_id": "16990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I consulted with Dr. Emily Carter at Westfield Clinic last year.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "239",
            "patient_id": "17001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 17,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 53,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 54,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Can you confirm if your email is kevin.adams@workmail.com?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "240",
            "patient_id": "17112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I visited the new clinic in Miami, FL, on June 8th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "241",
            "patient_id": "17223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 28,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's update your record with Dr. John Smith at Midtown Health Center.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "242",
            "patient_id": "17334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "This is Rajesh Patel. My phone number is +1-234-567-8901.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "243",
            "patient_id": "17445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 20,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 41,
                "end": 56,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Thank you, Rajesh. Let's check your previous records with ID RP890123.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "244",
            "patient_id": "17556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 17,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 61,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "ID"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My wife, Priya Sharma, has an appointment on March 22nd at City Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "245",
            "patient_id": "17667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 9,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 45,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 59,
                "end": 72,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Please confirm if your email is rajesh.patel@example.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "246",
            "patient_id": "17778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 32,
                "end": 56,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I was admitted to Sunshine Hospital on April 15th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "247",
            "patient_id": "17889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 18,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dr. Karen White referred you to Lakeside Clinic last year.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "248",
            "patient_id": "17990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 32,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 57,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My son's school is at 123 Maple Avenue, Springfield.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "249",
            "patient_id": "18001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 22,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The report indicates you were at Green Valley Hospital on January 1st.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "250",
            "patient_id": "18112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 58,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My ID number is KP567890, and I recently moved to Boston.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "251",
            "patient_id": "18223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 16,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "ID"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 56,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Can you recall when Dr. Mark Watson examined you last?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "252",
            "patient_id": "18334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 20,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "STAFF"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My daughter, Sophia Williams, is 12 years old and a patient here.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "253",
            "patient_id": "18445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 13,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "AGE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "You can reach the clinic by calling 444-789-1234 for any queries.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "254",
            "patient_id": "18556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 36,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dr. Alex Parker at Westfield Health Center suggested this treatment.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "255",
            "patient_id": "18667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 19,
                "end": 42,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Your last visit was on July 18th. Let's schedule a follow-up.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "256",
            "patient_id": "18778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 23,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My husband's name is Arjun Kumar, and he's in room 205.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "257",
            "patient_id": "18889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 21,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 46,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Did Dr. Michael Wilson oversee your care at General Hospital?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "258",
            "patient_id": "18990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 60,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My father, Henry Adams, is being treated for heart issues.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "259",
            "patient_id": "19001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Can you confirm your email is sophia.williams@mail.com?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "260",
            "patient_id": "19112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I traveled to Los Angeles, CA, on September 10th for a conference.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "261",
            "patient_id": "19223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 14,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 34,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Let's review the prescription from Dr. Linda Scott at Metro Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "262",
            "patient_id": "19334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 35,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 54,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I've been working late nights at Google, and now I feel drained.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "263",
            "patient_id": "19445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 33,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Are you eating properly? Also, when did you last visit Mercy Hospital?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "264",
            "patient_id": "19556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 55,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My name is Jacob Lee. I've been experiencing severe migraines lately.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "265",
            "patient_id": "19667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 20,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jacob, it seems you were admitted to Unity Health on January 3rd.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "266",
            "patient_id": "19778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 37,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 53,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jason, let's confirm the follow-up on June 3rd at Northside Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "371",
            "patient_id": "28889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 38,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm Claire Evans. My email is claire.evans@mail.com, and I need advice about my symptoms.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "372",
            "patient_id": "28990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 30,
                "end": 51,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Claire, let's discuss the details of your condition over a call this week.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "373",
            "patient_id": "28990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 64,
                "end": 73,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm James Bond, and I recently moved from Los Angeles to San Francisco.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "374",
            "patient_id": "29001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 14,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 42,
                "end": 53,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 57,
                "end": 70,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "James, your relocation updates have been recorded. Let's focus on your health goals.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "375",
            "patient_id": "29001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hi, I'm Olivia Chen. I have a consultation with Dr. Parker at Hillside Clinic.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "376",
            "patient_id": "29112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 48,
                "end": 58,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 62,
                "end": 77,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Olivia, the appointment with Dr. Parker is confirmed for July 12th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "377",
            "patient_id": "29112345"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 29,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "STAFF"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 57,
                "end": 66,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My brother, Chris Taylor, was recently treated for pneumonia at General Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "378",
            "patient_id": "29223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 12,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 64,
                "end": 80,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Chris's condition has improved. We'll follow up in three weeks.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "379",
            "patient_id": "29223456"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 62,
                "label": "TIMESTAMP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My employer, Sarah Johnson, is requesting a medical report for insurance purposes.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "380",
            "patient_id": "29334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 13,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sarah's request for the medical report has been processed and emailed.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "381",
            "patient_id": "29334567"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hi, my name is William Harris. My phone number is 987-654-3210.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "382",
            "patient_id": "29445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 15,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 50,
                "end": 62,
                "label": "PHONE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "William, let's review your test results and discuss further steps.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "383",
            "patient_id": "29445678"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My daughter, Lily Watson, is experiencing consistent headaches lately.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "384",
            "patient_id": "29556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 13,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lily's case requires a thorough examination. Let's schedule a session.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "385",
            "patient_id": "29556789"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "This is Kevin Brown. I've been having trouble sleeping for a week.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "386",
            "patient_id": "29667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kevin, we'll analyze your sleep patterns. Could you share a few more details?",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "387",
            "patient_id": "29667890"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My mother, Anna Scott, is scheduled for surgery on February 22nd at Green Valley Hospital.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "388",
            "patient_id": "29778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 51,
                "end": 64,
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 68,
                "end": 89,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Anna's procedure will be handled by a specialist. Everything is set for February 22nd.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "389",
            "patient_id": "29778901"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 72,
                "end": 85,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Hi, I'm Samantha Davis. I recently moved to Austin from Chicago.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "390",
            "patient_id": "29889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 8,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 44,
                "end": 50,
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 56,
                "end": 63,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Samantha, let's update your location in the system. Welcome to Austin!",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "391",
            "patient_id": "29889012"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 63,
                "end": 69,
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "My name is Jonathan Green. My email is jon.green@domain.com.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "392",
            "patient_id": "29990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 11,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 39,
                "end": 59,
                "label": "EMAIL"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jonathan, we'll use this email to send you the test reports.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "393",
            "patient_id": "29990123"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "I'm Isabella Torres. I visited Mercy Hospital on January 10th.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "394",
            "patient_id": "30001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 4,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 31,
                "end": 45,
                "label": "HOSP"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Isabella, the reports from Mercy Hospital confirm your recovery progress.",
        "meta": {
            "note_id": "395",
            "patient_id": "30001234"
        },
        "spans": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "start": 27,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "HOSP"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
